// Placeholder questions so we can test trivia game without relying on API
// for now.
const TEMP_QUESTIONS = [
  {
    "_id": "1a",
    "question": "Who is the only other player other than Jamal Murray to score 50 on less than 24 field goal attempts?",
    "answer": "ans1",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "2b",
    "question": "Who are the two players to have 25 point halves in a single playoff series?",
    "answer": "ans2",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "3c",
    "question": "Who was the NBA’s first ever unanimous mvp?",
    "answer": "ans3",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "4d",
    "question": "Who scored the NBA’s first ever three pointer and what year?",
    "answer": "ans4",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "5e",
    "question": "Who was the youngest player to score 10,000 points?",
    "answer": "ans5",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "6f",
    "question": "Who did the Los Angeles Lakers draft twice?",
    "answer": "ans6",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "7g",
    "question": "Who scored the most points in a single NBA game?",
    "answer": "ans7",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "8h",
    "question": "What team has the worst W-L percentage in NBA history?",
    "answer": "ans8",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "9i",
    "question": "Who has the most Finals MVP’s?",
    "answer": "ans9",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "_id": "10j",
    "question": "What franchise has the most HOF’s to date?",
    "answer": "ans10",
    "other": [
      "opt1",
      "opt2",
      "opt3"
    ]
  },
];

export default TEMP_QUESTIONS;
